Satoko's absent again today?
（圭一(けいいち)）沙都子(さとこ) 今日も休みなのか
（梨花(りか)）み～…
Mi.
（ﾚﾅ）風邪にしては長引くね
早く よくなるといいのに
She's been out a while for a cold.
I hope she gets well soon.
そうだな
Yeah.
（圭一）このときの俺には
想像もつかなかった
At the time, I didn't have a clue
as to what had befallen Satoko...
沙都子の身に降りかかっていること
...and what things
were bound to happen.
そして これから
起ころうとしている全てのことが
- "Curse Killing" Chapter -
Episode 02: BOND
When They Cry
Behind where I looked back
(who's there in the front)?
I raised my nails in the dark
(and slashed the night).
Raindrops become droplets of
blood and drip down the throat.
If you don't have
a place to go back to...
...then stop here on my finger.
I'll take you away
along with that finger.
To the unopenable
forest where cicadas cry.
You can't turn back anymore.
テイッ！
Here!
（岡村(おかむら)）さすが前原(まえばら)さん
（富田(とみた)）よっ！ 日本一ッス
- Yay, Maebara-san!
- You're the best in Japan!
Don't forget you owe me!
この貸し 忘れるでないぞ
（富田･岡村）
はい！ 一生 忘れません
Right, we'll never forget this!
まったく 調子のいいヤツらだぜ
They really know how to get by.
（大石(おおいし)）どうも こんにちは
（圭一）うん？
Hey. Hello.
（大石）お昼休み中 すみませんが
Sorry to bother you
during your lunch break.
Yeah.
私 興宮(おきのみや)警察署から
まいりました大石といいます
I'm from the Okinomiya
police department.
My name is Oishi.
職員室なら あっちですけど
The staff room is over there...
ああ…
いやいや そういうんじゃなくて
Oh, no, it's not that.
北条(ほうじょう)沙都子さん
呼んできてもらえませんか？
Could you call Satoko
Hojo-san out for me?
あっ…
警察が沙都子に何の用ですか？
What do the police
want with Satoko?
Oh, no, no. It's not a big deal.
あ～ いやいや
大した用事じゃないんですがね
ハァ… アポイントメントがないと
面会は かないませんか
I guess I'm not allowed to meet
with her without an appointment.
Oh, hello.
May I have a second?
ちょっと いいですかな？
北条沙都子さんを
呼んできてほしいんですがね
I'd like you to call
Satoko Hojo-san out for me.
Um, Hojo-san is absent today.
（生徒）えっと…
北条さんは今日 お休みですけど
休み？ いやはや
こいつはツイてないですね
Absent?
Oh, dear. I'm not
having much luck today.
…で ここにいる おにいさんは
何て名前か教えてくれますか？
Would you tell me the name
of this gentleman here?
前原圭一さんですけど…
It's Keiichi Maebara-san.
ああ あなた
ひょっとして前原屋敷の御曹子(おんぞうし)？
Oh, so you might be
the scion of the Maebara family.
I heard your father
is a famous artist.
お父さん
高名な芸術家さんなんですってねえ
だったら何ですか？
So what if he is?
こういう土地ではね
敵は作らないほうがいいですよ
You shouldn't be making
enemies in a place like this.
Otherwise...
さもないと…
（圭一）ウウッ…
You might have
some odd grudge...
妙な所で買った恨みが―
信じられない所で返ってくることが
あるかもしれませんよ
...come right back at you
when you least expect it.
I think you should stop there.
（入江(いりえ)）
それくらいになさったほうが
いいんじゃないですか？
うん？ おや…
Oh, if it isn't Dr. Irie.
これは 入江先生じゃないですか
I was thinking of coming by
your office later on as well.
先生の所にも あとで
お伺いしようと思っていたんですよ
We can't seem to have a nice
talk since you're always busy.
いつも お忙しいとかで
ろくろく お話ができませんからね
（入江）なら
令状をお持ちになったほうがいい
Then I suggest
you bring a warrant...
職務質問と任意同行は
拒否できますから
...since I can voluntarily refuse
questioning and going to the station.
（入江）大石蔵人(くらうど)という刑事です
（圭一）大石？
He's Kuraudo Oishi, a detective.
Oishi...
あんなに痛かったのに
アザひとつない
It hurt so much,
but there isn't a single bruise.
That man is used
to doing these things.
（入江）あの男は
こういうことに慣れてるんですよ
He said he wanted to see
Satoko about something.
あいつ
沙都子に用事があるとか言ってきて
Satoko-chan?
沙都子ちゃんに？
しつこい男だ
He's a stubborn man.
沙都子の所へ よく来るんですか？
Does he come
to see Satoko often?
前原さんは オヤシロさまの
たたりと 沙都子ちゃんの話
Maebara-san, have you heard
about Oyashiro-sama's curse...
...and Satoko-chan
at least a little?
少しは聞いたことがありますか？
ああ… 沙都子の両親が
ダム計画の賛成派で
Oh, you mean how Satoko's
parents were dam proponents...
転落事故で死んだのは―
...and Oyashiro-sama's curse
caused them to fall to their deaths.
オヤシロさまの
たたりだって話ですか？
ご両親が亡くなったあと
沙都子ちゃんとお兄さんの悟史(さとし)君は
After their parents
passed away...
...she and her brother moved in
with their uncle and his wife.
叔父夫婦宅に
身を寄せることになりましてね
えっ？ そうなんですか？
Really?
The uncle was her
father's younger brother.
叔父というのは 沙都子ちゃんの
お父さんの弟に当たる方なんですが
（圭一）初めて聞きました
I never heard that.
But I heard that life after that...
ただ そのあとの生活は
沙都子ちゃんたち兄妹(きょうだい)にとっては
...was very difficult for
Satoko-chan and her brother.
とても
つらいものだったと聞いています
えっ？ つらい生活って？
"Difficult life"?
Abuse.
虐待 …です
（圭一）ハッ…
However, luckily or unluckily...
ですが 幸か不幸か
その叔母が去年のお祭りの夜に―
On festival night
last year, the aunt...
覚醒剤の常用者に
殴り殺されたんです
...was beaten to death
by a drug addict.
The entire village
gossiped the death...
この死も 単なる殺人事件ではなく
オヤシロさまのたたりではないかと
村中で ささやかれました
...wasn't a simple murder case
but was Oyashiro-sama's curse.
叔父も オヤシロさまのたたりを
怖がり 雲隠れしてしまった
The uncle feared Oyashiro-sama's
curse and went into hiding.
聞いた話では
興宮の愛人宅に転がり込んでるとか
I heard he went crawling to his
mistress's place in Okinomiya.
それで 沙都子が解放されたと？
So then Satoko was freed.
はい　しかし…
Yes, but that man
started to appear...
まるで そのあとを継ぐように
あの男が現れるようになったんです
...as though he was
taking her uncle's place.
“あの男”？
That man?
大石ですよ
Oishi.
でも なんで あいつ 沙都子に
付きまとう必要があるんですか？
But why does he need
to follow Satoko around?
（岡村）ちょっと
気になるウワサを聞いたんスよ
I heard a rumor that worries me.
（圭一）ウワサ？
A rumor?
（富田）はい
帰ってきたらしいんですけど…
Yes. I heard he's back.
帰ってきたって 何が？
Who's back?
北条の叔父さんです
Hojo's uncle.
What does his return have
to do with Satoko's absence?
そいつが帰ってくるのと
沙都子の欠席と―
何か関係があるのかよ？
そ… それは分かりませんけど
I-I don't know about that...
分からないって何だよ！
（２人）ウワッ…
What do you mean
you don't know?
あっ… ごめん
Sorry.
No problem.
いえ…
Satoko...
沙都子…
（圭一）この家が…
This house is...
監督
Coach?
前原さん
こんな所で お会いするとは
Maebara-san.
I didn't expect to see you here.
沙都子
Satoko?
I coincidentally ran into the coach
on the way back from shopping.
（沙都子）買い物の帰りに
偶然 監督に お会いしたんですのよ
He said he'd drive me home,
so I gratefully accepted.
送ってくださるというので
お言葉に甘えたのですわ
A bicycle couldn't carry so much.
自転車では
こんなに運びきれませんからね
沙都子 これ…
（沙都子）えっ？
Satoko, this...
ハッ…
（鉄平(てっぺい)）ああ？
沙都子！
ヤカンかけっぱなしで出おったな
Satoko! You left
while the kettle was on!
You idiot!
この だらず！
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
すぐに買いに行けって言ったから…
You said to go
shopping right away, so...
Idiot!
ボケが！
（沙都子）アッ…
Well, well! If it isn't Dr. Irie!
おや？ 入江の先生じゃないですか
I coincidentally ran into Satoko.
沙都子ちゃんに
偶然 お会いしたもので
そうですか ハハハハッ…
Is that so?
Hey, Tecchan.
（鉄平の友人）おい 鉄ちゃん
What, Tsubaki?
You got a "riichi" again?
何ね？ ツバキ
あんた またリーチかいな
（沙都子）
街から 叔父さんのお友達が来てて
My uncle's friends
are visiting from town...
マージャンをやってますの
...and playing mahjong.
なんだよ それ！
自分は遊びほうけてて―
What's with that?
He's busy playing around and
makes you go buy this stuff?
沙都子に
こんなのを買いに行かせるのかよ
Those bruises...
What happened?
そのアザ どうしたんだよ？
おい！
（沙都子）ハッ…
Hey!
That jerk...
あの野郎！
気持ちは分かります
ですが 今は耐えてください
I know how you feel.
But please hold back for now.
Thank you, Keiichi-san.
ありがとうございますですわ
圭一さん
沙都子…
Satoko...
今 圭一さんが 本当の
にーにーみたいに見えました
Just now, you looked
like my real nii-nii.
私の本当の にーにーは
いなくなってしまったけど
My real nii-nii is gone, but I now
have a new nii-nii named Keiichi.
今は 圭一さんという
にーにーがいてくれる フフッ…
I'll never run away.
俺は 絶対に逃げないから
（鉄平）沙都子！
Satoko!
早(は)よう 乾き物(もん) 持ってこいよ
Hurry up and bring over the food!
ンッ… ええい
Where in the world
did Satoshi go?
（圭一）悟史は 一体
どこに行っちゃったんですか？
All we can say
is that he ran away.
家出した …としか言えません
If he was going to run away,
why didn't he take her too?
家出するなら なんで
沙都子も連れていかなかったんだ…
I bet Satoko thought the same
thing when she was left behind.
置いていかれた沙都子ちゃんも
同じ考えに至ったんでしょうね
That she was a burden to her
brother and was left behind.
“自分は
兄のお荷物だから捨てられた”と
No way...
そんな…
児童福祉法で
You can separate parent and
child under the child welfare act...
児童の安全を確保するために
緊急措置として―
...as an emergency measure
to ensure a child's safety...
親子を分離させるという方法が
あるそうなんですが
...but Satoko-chan
doesn't want that.
沙都子ちゃんが
それを望んでいません
沙都子が？
Satoko doesn't?
It seems she believes enduring
her uncle's abuse is her ordeal.
彼女は叔父のいじめに耐えることが
試練だと考えているようです
“誰にも頼らずに 自分の力だけで
試練を乗り越えたい”
She wants to overcome it alone,
without depending on others.
She believes without such strength,
Satoshi-kun won't return.
そういう力を身に着けなければ
悟史君は帰ってこないと
それじゃ 沙都子は…
So then Satoko...
（入江）虐待を認めない
...won't admit the abuse.
（圭一）そんな…
No way...
Of course, if the abuse is public,
the child consultation office...
（入江）もちろん児童相談所は―
虐待が公然の事実なら
沙都子ちゃんが否定しても―
...can forcibly take her into
protective custody despite that.
身柄は強制的に保護できるようです
しかし―
But for Satoko, that means
she's been defeated.
それは 沙都子ちゃんにとっては
負けを意味する
Her reason for living
is to become strong...
強くなって悟史君の帰りを待つのが
...and wait for
Satoshi-kun's return.
沙都子ちゃんの
生きる理由なんですよ
If I...
（圭一）俺は…
本当に沙都子が危ないと感じたら
迷わず通報します
...really feel that she's in danger,
I'll report it without hesitation.
その結果
沙都子が俺を恨むことになろうと
Even if she ends up
hating me as a result!
Why would you go so far...
どうして あなたは そこまで…
When They Cry
あれ？
Huh?
Oh, excuse me.
（富竹(とみたけ)）やあ 申し訳ない
君 雛見沢(ひなみざわ)の人だよね？
You're from Hinamizawa, right?
（圭一）そうですけど
Yes...
（富竹）古手(ふるで)神社って―
Can you tell me how to get to
Furude Shrine from here?
ここから どう行けばいいか
教えてもらえないかい？
If you don't mind
going together, I can take you.
一緒でよければ
連れていってあげますけど
I'm Tomitake,
a freelance photographer.
僕は富竹　フリーの
カメラマンをやっているんだ
I'm Maebara.
前原です
（鷹野(たかの)）あら 前原君じゃない？
（圭一）あっ…
Oh, if it isn't Maebara-kun.
Hello.
（鷹野）こんにちは
Oh, do you know each other?
あれ？ 知り合いかい？
（圭一）えっ？ その…
Um...
私のこと まだ思い出せない？
You still can't remember me?
ウフフッ…
（圭一）はぁ？
鷹野三四(みよ)さんだよ
村の診療所に勤めてる
Miyo Takano-san.
She works at the village clinic.
I don't blame you.
ムリないわね　道で
何度か すれ違ったくらいだから
We've only passed
a few times on the road.
（圭一）そうなんですか
Oh, I see.
It seems you're pretty famous.
（富竹）君は結構 有名人らしいね
（圭一）えっ？
（鷹野）ウフッ… なんてったって
前原屋敷の御曹子ですものね
Why of course, since you're
the scion of the Maebara family.
Are you two colleagues?
お２人は写真仲間ですか？
仲間だなんて とんでもない
Oh, we're no colleagues.
I'm just a beginner
being introduced to it.
素人の私が
手ほどきをしてもらってるだけよ
あさってから綿流しだろう
The cotton drifting
starts in two days, right?
I plan to take pictures
starting with tomorrow's setup.
あしたの設営シーンから
レンズに収めるつもりなんだよ
オヤシロさまに感謝するための
お祭りでしたっけ？
The festival for paying thanks
to Oyashiro-sama, right?
Yes, the festival to pay
thanks to Oyashiro-sama.
そう オヤシロさまに
感謝するためのお祭り
村の敵に
たたりをなすオヤシロさまか
Oyashiro-sama, who curses
the village's enemies, huh?
今年もあるとしたら
誰になるだろうね
If it happens again this year,
I wonder who it will be...
Those incidents?
（圭一）あの一連の事件ですか？
（鷹野）ええ
Yes.
（圭一）たたりなんかで
人が死ぬんですかね？
Can someone die from
something like a curse?
（富竹）でも
事件は実際に起こってたんだろう？
But those incidents
really did occur, right?
What if, for instance, someone is
imitating the curse to kill people?
例えば誰かが たたりに なぞらえて
殺しているとしたら？
えっ？
鷹野さんは何か知ってるんですか？
Do you know
something, Takano-san?
うん？ 教えてあげても よくってよ
ウフフッ…
I don't mind telling
you if you want.
I was really worried that you
were going to be absent too.
（梨花）圭一まで欠席なのかと
とても心配しましたのですよ
（ﾚﾅ）沙都子ちゃん
I heard Satoko...
風邪が長引いてるって
連絡があったらしいよ
...called in and said her cold
seems to be lasting longer.
かわいそうなので
Since we feel bad for her, we
were talking about visiting her.
みんなで お見舞いに行こうという
話が出ていますのですよ
何言ってんだよ？ 梨花ちゃん
（ﾚﾅ）うん？
What are you saying, Rika-chan?
All of you know Satoko
really isn't sick, right?
みんなだって
沙都子が風邪じゃないことは―
知ってるんだろう？ 二度と
そういう しらじらしいこと言うな
Don't ever say such
shameless things again!
Who'd you hear that from?
誰から聞いたの？
昨日 見てきた
I saw yesterday.
It's not just you, Keiichi-kun.
圭一君だけじゃないよ
It's hard for everyone.
みんな つらいよ
ごめん
I'm sorry.
（ベルの音）
（魅音）起立！ 礼！
Stand! Bow!
（生徒たち）さようなら
Goodbye.
Kei-chan, let's go home. You're
not up for club activities, right?
圭ちゃん 帰ろう　部活…
する気にもならないでしょう？
Oh, Mion, can I come
over to your house today?
あっ 魅音 今日さ
お前の家(うち)に寄ってもいいか？
漫画…
少し まとめて借りたいんだけど
I want to borrow some manga...
えっ？ いいけど
Sure.
Sonozaki
（魅音）…で なに？
So what's up?
You had something
to discuss, right?
圭ちゃん
何か話があったんでしょう？
I do.
（圭一）ある
かなり本気な話が
Something quite serious.
突然な話で
面食らうかもしれないけど
You might be bewildered
at such a sudden topic...
聞いてほしい
...but I'd like you to listen.
As the next family head and
leader of the three great families...
鬼ヶ淵(おにがふち)村御三家の 今や筆頭であり
その次期当主の園崎(そのざき)魅音に…
...of Onigafuchi Village,
Mion Sonozaki.
Where'd you hear that?
どこで聞いたの？
（圭一）えっ？
それは… 関係ないことだ
That's irrelevant.
It seems you know a lot about
me that may be true or not.
私について いろいろと
あること ないこと知ってそうだね
…で 何を言いたいの？
So what are you trying to say?
オヤシロさまのたたりって…
あるよな？
You know about
Oyashiro-sama's curse, right?
If this year's curse isn't
set to fall on Satoko's uncle...
もしも 今年のたたりが
沙都子の叔父じゃなかったら
沙都子の叔父に変えてくれ
...please change it to him.
I-I heard that
Oyashiro-sama's curse is...
お… 俺 聞いたんだ
オヤシロさまのたたりって…
その…
Um...
“園崎家が主導で 御三家が
起こしている村ぐるみの事件だ”
That they're caused by
the three great families...
...led by the Sonozakis,
and the whole village, right?
…でしょう？
I-I'm not interested in
whether you're involved or not.
べ… 別に俺は―
それに魅音が関わってるとか
そんなのには興味がないんだ
ただ もしも そういうたたりを
決めている連中に渡りがつくなら
But if you can contact those
who choose the curse's target...
沙都子の叔父を選ぶように
言ってほしいだけなんだ　頼む！
...I just want you to tell them to
choose Satoko's uncle. Please!
Are you calling me
a murderer, Kei-chan?
圭ちゃんは
私を人殺し呼ばわりするんだ？
魅音が 連続殺人の
主犯だろうと 無関係だろうと―
I don't care whether you're
the ringleader or not involved!
俺は どうでもいいんだ
俺は ただ 沙都子を助けたい
I just want to save Satoko!
So curse Satoko's
uncle this year...
だから
沙都子の叔父を今年のたたりに…
Stop.
ストップ
（圭一）えっ？
I'd like to prepare dinner soon,
so could you leave for today?
そろそろ 夕飯の準備をしたいから
今日のところは帰ってくれないかな
魅音…
Mion...
I totally understand how you feel.
圭ちゃんの気持ちは
痛いくらい分かったよ
もしも 本当に私が
圭ちゃんの言うように―
If I really were, as you say,
in the position to manipulate...
御三家を操って 毎年の犠牲者を
選べる立場にあったなら
...the three great families'
choice of victim...
...then I'd probably
grant your wish.
きっと
私は 圭ちゃんの願いをかなえるよ
Mion!
魅音…
But the reality is different.
でも 現実は違う
私は ただの園崎魅音
I'm just Mion Sonozaki.
It's true there are various bad
rumors about the Sonozakis...
確かに園崎家は―
いろいろな意味で 悪いウワサを
持っている一族だけれども
人殺しなんて大それたこと…
...but we'd never do something
as appalling as murder.
絶対にやらないよ
ごめん…
I'm sorry.
Oh, those are Satoko's shoes!
あっ… 沙都子ちゃんの靴あるよ
ねっ？
（魅音）ホントだ
- Right?
- You're right.
We can't say much
just because she's back.
来てるだけじゃ分からないだろう
Satoko!
沙都子！
Mi.
何なんですの？
朝っぱらから騒がしいですわね
What is it?
It's only the morning,
but you're all so noisy.
Satoko-chan.
沙都子ちゃん
Who called
the child probation officer?
保護司 呼んだのは どなたですの？
まったく とんだ騒ぎでしたのよ
Honestly, it was such a mess.
保護司？ 来たのか？
A child probation officer came?
Out of the blue, and my uncle
and I were very annoyed.
急に押しかけられて
私も叔父さまも
とんだ迷惑でしたのよ もう
Jeez.
What happened to your uncle?
叔父さんは どうなったの？
We admitted some
misunderstandings...
多少 誤解があったことを認めて
２人で ごめんなさいをしましたわ
...and both apologized.
Mi.
何だよ？ 梨花ちゃん
What, Rika-chan?
Satoko told the officer nothing
was wrong and sent them away.
（梨花）沙都子は
保護司に 何でもないと言って―
追い返してしまいました
（圭一）誰が呼んだんだ？
Who called them?
（梨花）知恵(ちえ)先生です
（知恵）ハァ…
Chie-sensei.
She knew?
（圭一）知ってたのか？
Despite looks,
she's the homeroom teacher.
ああ見えても 一応は担任ですから
She sent them
away herself, huh?
（圭一）それを
追い返してしまったのか 自分で
Yes.
（梨花）はいです
But no matter how she denies it,
the abuse is a fact, right?
（圭一）だけど いくら沙都子が
否定したって 虐待は事実だろう
これで３回目なのです
This is the third time.
There were two reports of Satoko
and child abuse in the past.
沙都子の児童虐待の通報は
過去にも２度あったのです
過去？
（梨花）はい
- In the past?
- Yes.
死んでしまったお父さんのときにも
Even with her late father.
死んでしまったお父さんは沙都子の
本当のお父さんではないのです
Her late father
wasn't her real father.
Satoko's mother had remarried.
（梨花）
沙都子のお母さんは 再婚なのです
沙都子と悟史は
お母さんの連れ子で
Satoko and Satoshi
were born before that...
お父さんと
血は つながっていなかったのです
...and had no blood
ties to their father.
沙都子は
叔父夫婦に預けられる以前も―
Even before Satoko was in her
uncle and his wife's care...
家族と あまり
良好な関係ではなかったのです
...she didn't have
a good family relationship.
In order to trick her stepfather...
沙都子は 義理のお父さんを
陥れるのを目的に―
...Satoko made up an abuse story
and called the abuse hotline...
ウソの虐待話を作って
自分で虐待ＳＯＳに電話したのです
...but the officer
found out the truth.
それが保護司にバレて…
（圭一）…で 今回も
ウソだと思われてるってことか？
Then they think it's a lie again?
（梨花）それは分かりませんが
I don't know,
but at the very least...
少なくとも 緊急保護は
されなかったんだと思います
...I think she wasn't
put in protective custody.
What's with that?
なんだよ それ
つまり 沙都子は
ウソをつくかもしれないから―
Then that means
since Satoko might lie...
...they're just
observing the case?
様子を見てるってことかよ？
（梨花）うん…
沙都子…
Satoko...
Well, it's time for lunch.
（沙都子）
さぁて お昼でございますわね
Mi.
み～
（沙都子）ウフフッ…
はぅ～！ 見て見て
今日はオムライスなんだよ
Look, look!
It's omelet rice today!
Nice, Rena!
（沙都子）さすがレナさん
これなら いつお嫁に行っても
おかしくない腕前ですわ
Becoming a bride at any
time would be no surprise.
（ﾚﾅ）えっ？ レナが お嫁さん？
Me, a bride?
沙都子
Satoko...
Nii-nii.
沙都子ちゃん？
Satoko-chan?
（うめき声）
おい どうしたんだよ？
Hey, what's wrong?
オエッ！
- Satoko!
- Satoko-chan...
（魅音）沙都子！
（ﾚﾅ）沙都子ちゃん…
さ… 沙都子 大丈夫か？
S-Satoko, are you all right?
No!
（突き飛ばす音）
（沙都子）イヤー！
（魅音）
沙都子 あんた どうしちゃったの！
Satoko, what's wrong with you?
もうイヤ イヤ イヤ…
No more... No... No...
No.
イヤです… イヤ イヤ イヤ…
No... No... No...
No...
イヤ…
（圭一）沙都子
Satoko...
ご… ごめんなさい ごめんなさい
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい
I-I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry...
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい
ごめんなさい
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい…
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
沙都子…
Satoko...
To get my happiness,
I had done everything...
...but had done nothing
to be blamed and accused of.
The sound of footsteps
became louder every day.
Then I noticed the fact
there was no time.
I was a believer in life,
to be myself always.
And was asking
whether I would be alive.
Give me a reason
why not to adopt in this way.
Or judge me to be guilty
of so many incurable sins.
Tell me why or why not?
Complaining way too much.
Maybe I overlooked
something fatal for me.
Preview
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
求めたのは いつもの まどろみ
Preview
What was sought
was the usual daze.
What's heard is
the sound of malicious rain.
流されたのは 暗闇への扉
What drifted away
was the door to darkness.
When They Cry.
｢ひぐらしのなく頃に｣
"Curse Killing" Chapter,
Episode 3: BORDERLINE.
- "Curse Killing" Chapter -
Episode 03: BORDERLINE
"Curse Killing" Chapter,
Episode 3: BORDERLINE.
Can you believe it?
あなたは信じられますか？